Каждый, кто сделал тебе больно покойник
Everyone who hurt you is dead
Укрою тебя пледом, посажу на подоконник
I'll cover you with a blanket, sit you on the windowsill
Залезу под свитер, в самое сердце
I'll crawl under the sweater, into the very heart
Ты холодный Питер, но в тебе можно согреться
You're cold St. Petersburg, but one can warm up in you
Каждый шрамом на запястье остался
Each remained as a scar on the wrist
Я убью всех тех, кто посмел тебя касаться
I will kill all those who dared to touch you
Мятые простыни, отключили свет
Crumpled sheets; they turned off the lights
Мы друг для друга созданы, бракованный дуэт
We're made for each other, a defective duet
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
Привяжу тебя к себе, чтоб не боялась темноты
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты…
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
Привяжу тебя к себе, чтоб не боялась темноты
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты…
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…
Я бы хотела стать твоим одеялом
I would like to become your blanket
Чтобы ночью ты со мной спала и не замерзала
So you sleep with me at night and don't get cold
Согреть тебя тем, что от меня осталось
To warm you with what's left of me
Лишь бы ты не заболела, лишь бы утром улыбалась
Just so you don't fall ill, just so you smile in the morning
Я бы хотела жить с тобой в одном теле
I would like to live with you in one body
Игнорировать соседей, что стучат по батареям
Ignoring the neighbors who bang on the radiators
Днём или ночью это неважно
By day or by night — it doesn't matter
Я так счастлива с тобой в этой большой многоэтажке
I'm so happy with you in this big high-rise
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
Привяжу тебя к себе, чтоб не боялась темноты
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты…
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…
У-у-у
Ooh
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
Привяжу тебя к себе, чтоб не боялась темноты
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты…
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you
Привяжу тебя к себе, чтоб не боялась темноты
I'll tie you to me so you aren't afraid of the dark
Чай на столе, жаль, что не ты…
Tea on the table — a pity it's not you…